Maria Veronica Sonzini

59 Longacres, st Albans. AL4 0SL

Mobile 07492303735

mavesonzini@gmail.com

https://github.com/mavesonzini

Profile

Due to my mixed experience in sciences, as a former Radiographer, and technology as a developer, I am a valuable asset to any team. QA and Testing Experience in Hewlett Packard. Software developer (Ruby on Rails, swift -iOS-, JavaScript)

Experience

Grow App - 2014-2016

Freelance (remote) as iOS Developer, assisting in Bug Fixing and the creation of mobile applications for iPad and iPhone.

Some applications I have worked on:

Inkit (similar to Pinterest, for people who want to share tattoo images)

This Weekend (Social network)

Monedas blue (currency exchange rates)

TeleMater (Single page app, implementing a web view)

Software tester, Hewlett-Packard Argentina-2012 - 2015

Assessed and contributed for user experience on over 20 application projects. Planned and designed over 500 test cases for multiple projects. 2 years experience in QA and Software testing for Santander Río (ISBAN) account, testing the ATM hardware/software functionality (TAS), the automated payment to suppliers (TAP) and the internal administration system.

Worked for over 1,000 hours on the Copa Airlines project, designing and executing test cases for SAP implementation on the airline's administrative system.

Used Hewlett Packard programs: ALM 11, UFT, QTP, Sprinter.

General Radiographer Internship, Hospital Misericordia, Córdoba Argentina – 2011-2012 1 year General Radiologic Internship working 12 hours a week.

Experience with General Radiography, working with patients in ICU, accident and emergency department (mobile radiography) and outpatients (fixed radiography). Digital and manual radiography processing.

Education

Universidad Nacional de Cordoba, Argentina – General Radiographer Technologist, 2015 Diagnosing and treating diseases and injuries using medical imaging techniques, such as x-rays, computed tomography (CT), magnetic resonance imaging (MRI), nuclear medicine, positron emission tomography (PET) and ultrasound.

Junior Softer development, Maker's Academy, London - 2016-2017

Makers Academy is Europe's leading Web Developer bootcamp. Some of the web applications I have worked on during the bootcamp:

Yelp clone (Ruby on rails, Amazon web services, TDD, Facebook API, Devise)

Airbnb clone (Ruby, TDD, Javascript web services)

Skills

Software Development:

Intimate knowledge of object-oriented design principles and common design patterns.

Knowledge of Web technologies.

Ability to learn processes and systems quickly.

Developing software systems.

Able to work in a fast-paced challenging environment.

Can work independently as well as under the direction of senior IT architects.

Ruby

Ruby on Rails

Git

Javascript

TDD

Database modelling

Debugging

Data structures

References

Cristian Pena, Deloitte Digital UK +44 47971179883